

### **Thomas Miller** Frontend Web Developer

thomas.miller147@gmail.com



+41795602071



http://thomasmiller.ch



Rue de la Sionge 12, 1630 Bulle



https://github.com/Meuss

# ① Overview

I am a very passionate frontend web developer from Switzerland. With a Bachelor of Arts in Information Systems Management, I became a self-taught developer through tutorials and courses on the internet, learning how to build visually attractive, interactive and responsive websites. I have been employed since 2015 as a frontend web developer and have been doing freelance projects on the side. I am currently looking to integrate a new team with people like me, passionate about the web and working on interesting projects. My goal is to keep expanding my knowledge about UX/UI design, animations, improve my coding skills while learning new technologies and frameworks.

### **Education**

**Bachelor of Arts** 2010-2014 Information Systems Management University of Fribourg

**Federal Maturity** 2003-2008

Minor: Spanish Collège du Sud, Bulle

# Languages

### Bilingual English / French

Good German knowledge (B1) Basic Spanish knowledge











## Experience

### **Frontend Developer @ macmac ltd** June 2015 - Today

I worked on different types of projects, creating interactive and responsive websites for different corporations. I mostly worked on turning outdated joomla websites into responsive, up-to-date websites using either WordPress or Kirby CMS. I put in place the designs that our designer had prepared, adding my own animations and input. I learned how to use git for version control, css preprocessors (SASS) as well as build tools such as gulp.

### **Auxiliary Employee @ denner ag** 2010-2014

Part-time job at Avry-Centre during my University studies.

# Favorite Workflow / Libraries / Tools

css preprocessors (SASS) build tools (gulp+ npm+browsersync) libraries (jquery, greensock, bootstrap) tools (ST3/Atom, PS, Sketch) version control (git) cms(Kirby, WordPress, Woocommerce)





































